The <adjective> did not <verb>. 
It was too wet to play. 
So we sat in the <noun> 
All that cold, cold, wet day. 
I sat there with <girl's name>. 
We sat there, we two. 
And I said, “How I wish 
We had something to do!” 
Too wet to go out 
And too cold to play <sport>. 
So we sat in the <noun>.  
We did nothing at all.  
So all we could do was to  
Sit! Sit! Sit! Sit! 
And we did not like it. 
Not one little bit.  
And then 
Something went <loud noise>! 